菲比，在单身女士派对上…
So, Pheebs, I was just at this bachelorette party...
…有个蛋糕的造型像男人的…
...and they had a cake that was in the shape of a man's...
…那个东西
...thing-a-ding-ding.
我就想啊，你会怎么认为呢?
And I was wondering, what would you have thought of that?
令人作呕还是好玩?
Offensive or amusing?
我不知道．莫妮卡，你怎么看?
I'm not sure. Monica, what do you think?
-有点俗气 -该死
- Sounds kind of tacky. - Damn it.
看能不能取消掉，要是不能 她们都会看着那讨厌的“东西”
I'll see if they can cancel it. If not, maybe they can put eyes on the "hoojies"...
我们只能说那是某种奇异的大象
...and we'll just say it's just some sort of weird elephant.
大伙们，你们一定不会相信!
Guys, you won't believe this!
-我刚刚跟我的经纪人谈过...-我的天啊!
- I just talked to my agent... - Oh, my God!
对不起，太快了，你说吧
I'm sorry. Too soon. You go.
我因为《我们的日子》被提名!
I got nominated for Days of our Lives!
这真的是太好了! 恭喜你
- Good for you! - Congratulations!
我不敢相信你获得艾美奖（美国电视届最高奖项）提名!
I can't believe you're nominated for an Emmy!
-肥皂剧文摘奖? -不，我被提名“肥皂奖”
- Soap Opera Digest Award? - Nope. I'm up for a "Soapie."
那是你乱编的吗?
Is that something you're making up?
不，它是真的，这个奖从1998年开始颁发
No, no, no, it's real! And it has been, since 1998.
他们不会取消那个蛋糕
Okay, they said they won't cancel the cake...
不过我们可以在旁边写上“美国国家航空航天局”
...but I was thinking we could write "NASA" on the side...
-然后送给罗斯 - 好的
- and then give it to Ross. - Okay. Yeah.
嘿，瑞秋，我被提名肥皂奖了!
Hey, Rach! I'm up for a Soapie!
我的天啊!
Oh, my God!
天啊! 那是排名第三的肥皂剧大奖!
Oh, my God! That's the third most prestigious soap opera award there is!
谢谢! 我猜我们知道我该带谁参加颁奖典礼
Thank you! I guess we know who I'll take to the awards!
别跟我开这种玩笑! 所有明星都会去吗?
Don't kid about that! Will all the stars be there?
很多人都说他们会去
Many are scheduled to appear.
-我不能去，我一定会太紧张！ -那就换我去吧
- I can't go. I'll be too nervous! - I'll go.
你要结婚了，那个机会是我的
You're getting married. This is all I have.
-我们要举行庆祝 -对! 我们送你一个蛋糕，
- We should celebrate. - Yes! And we will get you a cake...
造型是麦克风
...in the shape of a microphone.
还有两个网球
With two tennis balls.
Friends S07E18 乔伊的奖
The One With Joey's Award
恩斯特・穆伯拉特假设迅猛龙受到威胁时…
Ernest Muhlbrat hypothesized that the velociraptor, when threatened...
它会把颈部肌肉张开，发出尖锐的叫声…
...would expand its collar and emit a high-pitched noise...
将敌人吓跑
...to frighten off predators.
路易斯，什么事?
Mr. Lewis?
它是怎么叫的?
What kind of noise?
它会发出尖锐嘈杂的声音
Just a high-pitched, intimidating noise.
那到底是什么样子?
But like how?
我们并不确定
Well, we don't know for sure.
但我想，应该是这样的
But in my head, it sounded something like this:
当然，这只是种猜测
Of course, this is just conjecture.
好了，今天的课上到这里
Okay. That's all for today.
摩斯，我能跟你谈谈吗?
Mr. Morse, can I see you for a moment?
什么事? 教授
Yes, sir?
我得跟你谈谈你的期中成绩
I need to talk to you about your midterm exam.
-恐怕我得让你不及格 -为什么?
- I'm afraid I had to fail you. - Why?
你得答中百分之六十才能过关
Well, you need 60% to pass.
-我的分数是多少? -七
- What did I get? - Seven.
那不是很好
That's not so good.
不，那糟透了，奈德，到底发生了什么事?
No, no, it's not. What happened, Ned?
或许你可以饶我一次，我恋爱了
Maybe you can cut me some slack. I'm sort of in love.
抱歉，但那真的不是我的问题
I'm sorry, but that's really not my problem.
我爱上了你
I'm in love with you.
那好像跟我有一点关系
That brings me in the loop a little.
所以我才会考那么烂，我没办法专心上课
That's why I did so bad on this test. I'm having a hard time concentrating.
你站在讲台上讲课的时候…
When you're up there and you're teaching...
表情是那么得严肃…
...and your face gets all serious...
你看起来好帅 当你穿着高长领毛衣时
You look so good. When you wear that tight little turtleneck sweater...
我是你的老师，对不起
I'm your teacher. I'm sorry.
你是学生
You're a student.
而且我喜欢女人
And I like women.
虽然有人在椅背上写了一些话
In spite of what may be written on the backs of these chairs.
吧台那个男人在看你
That guy at the counter's totally checking you out.
真的吗?
Really?
-我的天啊，他真的好帅! -去吧
- Oh, my God, he's really cute! - Go for it.
菲比，我订婚了
Phoebe, I'm engaged.
我建议你去问他的电话号码 以防万一
I'm saying, get his number, just in case.
说不定钱德发生意外 丧失了性能力…
But if Chandler's in an accident and can't perform sexually...
他要你找个爱人 满足他无法满足你的那个部份
...he'd want you to take a lover to satisfy needs he'd no longer fulfill.
我能跟你说句话吗?
Can I just tell you something?
我真的受宠若惊，但我订婚了
I'm very flattered, but I'm engaged.
这真的是很尴尬
This is kind of embarrassing.
事实上，我想跟你朋友说话
I actually came over to talk to your friend.
你是应该觉得尴尬
You should be embarrassed.
-我以为你知道我在看你 -我知道，但那真的很好玩
- I thought you knew I looked at you. - I did, but that was really fun.
“得奖的是…乔伊崔比亚尼”
"The winner is... Joey Tribbiani!"
我真的没想到我会得奖…
"I honestly never expected this.
我没有准备演讲稿…
I didn't prepare a speech.
我要谢谢我的父母，他们一直支持我…
I'd like to thank my parents, who've always been there for me.
我还要谢谢我的朋友 钱德，莫妮卡，菲比，瑞秋
Also like to thank my friends, Chandler, Monica, Phoebe, Rachel..."
-我排在第四个? -天啊!
- I'm fourth? - Jeez!
看看你，拿着枫糖奖杯
Look at you with your maple syrup award!
拜托你不要告诉别人这件事
Maybe you don't tell anyone about this?
那没有什么大不了的 我也会拿着洗发水的瓶子那么做
No big deal. I do that with my shampoo bottle.
-真的吗? -没错
- Really? - Yeah.
-你假装自己得了什么奖? -格莱美奖（美国音乐最高奖）
- What award are you practicing for? - Grammy.
最佳新进艺人
For Best New Artist.
肥皂奖的人今天打电话给我 我还得上台颁奖
The Soapies people called today. I also get to present an award.
所以就算你没得奖，你也有机会上台
So you'll get on stage even if you don't win.
-你以为我不会得奖? -你当然会得奖
- You don't think I'll win? - Of course I do.
但最受欢迎死而复生奖？ 那个奖的竞争很激烈
But Favorite Returning Character? That's a tough category.
你要跟一个火葬了之后还能活过来的人竞争
You're up against the guy who survived his own cremation.
不，我知道或许我不会得奖，但那只是…
No, I know I might not win. But it's just...
我从来没有被提名过，我真的很想得奖
I've never been nominated. I want it so much.
或许你会得奖
You'll probably get it.
但你应该开始练习你的“优雅的失败者”表情
But you should start practicing your "gracious-loser" face.
当摄影机拍到你时，你得表现出失望的样子
When the cameras are on you, you want to look disappointed.
但也得表现出对方是实至名归的表情，就像这样
But also that your colleague deserved to win. Like:
你知道吗?
You know?
-你也练过没得到格莱美奖？ -不，我是格莱美奖的常胜军
- You practice losing the Grammys too? - No, at the Grammys, I always win.
嘿，莫妮卡，这个女人只吃了两口牛排
Hey, Mon. This woman only had two bites of her steak.
-要我打包给你的狗吗? -好的
- Want me to wrap it up for your dog? - Oh, yeah.
-你的狗叫什么名字来着? -乔伊
- What's your dog's name again? - Joey.
-嘿 -你跟杰克约会还顺利吗?
- Hey! - How'd your date go with Jake?
太棒了，我们一直注视着彼此
Great. We couldn't keep our eyes off each other.
每隔一阵子他就会靠过来摸我的头发跟脖子
Every once in a while, he'd lean over, stroke my hair, then touch my neck.
住手，你害得我好痒
Stop it. You're getting me all tingly.
我只能想：他要吻我了吗?
All I could think of was, is he gonna kiss me?
-他吻了你吗? -我是个淑女 绝不会泄露那种事
- Did he? - I'm a lady. I don't kiss and tell.
但这个吻痕说明了一切
But this hickey speaks for itself.
好了，我知道了
Okay, I got it. I got it.
我真的好喜欢他 感觉上像是我今天喝了十杯酒
I like him so much, I feel like I've had 10 drinks today.
我只喝了六杯
I've only had six.
我第一次跟钱德约会后再也没有那样的感觉
I haven't had that feeling since I first went out with Chandler.
-我永远都不会再有那样的感觉 -你的口气跟男人一模一样
- I'll never have that feeling again. - You sound like a guy.
不，男人会说“我永远都不能再跟别人上床”
No, a guy would say, "I'll never get to sleep with anyone else."
我永远都不能再跟别人上床!
I'll never sleep with anyone else!
-你现在才知道吗? -不，也许．是的!
- Are you just realizing this now? - No. Maybe. Yes!
我一直忙着筹备婚礼完全忘了我要放弃什么
I'm so busy planning the wedding, I forgot about what I'll give up.
我再也不会有初吻
I'll never have a first kiss again.
你会有最后的吻别
You'll have a last kiss.
我能问你一件事吗? 有男人喜欢过你吗?
Can I ask you something? Has a guy ever had a crush on you?
那就是你要帮我打领结的原因?
Is that why you wanted to tie my tie?
我班上的学生说他爱上我了
A kid in my class said he's in love with me.
哇
Whoa!
-哇什么? -罗斯有男朋友了
- Whoa, what? - Ross has a boyfriend!
我没有男朋友
I do not have a boyfriend.
我班上有个男学生暗恋我
There's a guy in one of my classes who has a crush on me.
-真的吗? -对
- Really? - Yeah.
去年是伊莉莎白，现在是这个孩子…
Last year, Elizabeth, now this kid...
这是怎么一回事? 我散发出…
What is it? Am I giving out some kind of...
性感教授的气质吗?
...sexy-professor vibe?
现在看起来不像
Not right now.
重点是我的自然魅力让他期中考试不及格
The point is, my natural charisma has made him fail his midterm.
我为那孩子感到难过
Now I feel bad for the kid.
我也曾经暗恋过老师，那真的很难受
I had a crush on a teacher once, and it was so hard.
我没办法专心上课，每次他看着我时我都会脸红
I couldn't concentrate. I blushed every time he looked at me.
你还记得十九岁时的恋爱滋味吧
You remember what it's like to be 19 and in love.
-我可以放他一马 -太棒了
- I can cut him some slack. - Yeah.
-你怎么忘记那个老师的? -我没有，我跟他上床了
- How'd you get over that teacher? - I didn't. I got under him.
问题解决了
Problem solved.
-再见，菲比，-好的，再见
- Bye, Phoebe. - Okay, bye.
-好的，再见 -再见
- All right. Bye. - Bye.
再见!
Bye!
-再见! -我会想你的!
- Bye! - I'll miss you!
我也会想你的!
I'll miss you too!
我们在门边说再见，是不想炫耀我们的新恋情
We said goodbye at the door so as not to flaunt our new love.
没关系，你不必顾忌我
It's okay. You don't have to tiptoe around me.
我已经想过了，你知道吗?
I've thought about it. You know what?
我可以接受没有心动感觉的生活
I'm okay, not having that new-relationship feeling.
-我已经开始想你了! -我也会想你!
- I miss you already! - I miss you too!
那真的太棒了 但我不会拿我的幸福跟你交换
That's great, but I wouldn't trade what I have for that.
我会一辈子跟钱德相守，那让我觉得幸福
I'll be with Chandler the rest of my life. That makes me happy.
快坐下，我们正在谈我们的关系有多深厚…
Come sit down. We're talking about how our relationship's deep...
是那么得有意义，真的是那样，你觉得呢?
...and meaningful. It is, don't you think?
哦，一点都没错
Oh, totally.
拉一下我的手指（意思是否定刚才所说的话）
Pull my finger.
好了，各位，我们30分钟后回来
Okay, everybody, we're back in 30.
你去哪里了? 他们刚要颁奖给我
Where have you been? They're about to give out my award.
我在洗手间，苏珊・卢斯刚好出来
Oh, well, I was in the bathroom, and Susan Lucci came out of a stall...
她的鞋上有纸巾，所以我就拿了
...and she had toilet paper on her shoe, so I took it.
-最受欢迎死而复生的男演员… -轮到我了!
- Favorite Returning Male... - This is my category!
-你的演讲稿带了吗? -带了
- Got your speech? - Got my speech.
优雅的失败者练习好了吗?
Got your gracious-loser face?
记住，如果你得奖了，你得抱我
Try to remember, if you win, you have to hug me.
我能捏你的屁股吗?
Can I squeeze your ass?
在电视上吗?
On TV?
可以!
Yeah!
他们说你不能再回家去了
They say you can't go home again...
这四位杰出的演员证明了也不尽是如此
...but these four exceptional actors have proven that this is not always the case.
在最受欢迎死而复生男演员奖方面被提名的有
In the Favorite Returning Male character category, the nominees are:
约翰惠勒《综合医院》（1963年开播）
John Wheeler from General Hospital.
盖文葛拉姆《年少轻狂》（1973年开播）
Gavin Graham from The Young and the Restless.
唐肯哈灵顿《热情》（1999年开播）
Duncan Harrington from Passions.
乔伊崔比亚尼《我们的日子》（1965年开播）
And Joey Tribbiani from Days of our Lives.
得奖的是
And the Soapie goes to:
盖文葛拉车《年少轻狂》
Gavin Graham from The Young and the Restless.
搞什么…?
What the...?!
颁发最受欢迎女配角奖的是：
Presenting the Favorite Supporting Actress award:
《我们的日子》的乔伊崔比亚尼
Joey Tribbiani from Days of our Lives.
所有在这个奖项被提名的优秀女演员…
Any one of the brilliant actresses nominated for this award...
得奖都是实至名归，可惜只有一个人能得奖
...deserves to take it home. Unfortunately, only one can.
最受欢迎女配角奖被提名的有：
The nominees for Favorite Supporting Actress are:
《热情》，艾玲高菲
From Passions, Erin Goff.
《一生只活一次》（1968年开播）玛丽罗琳毕雪 《我所有的孩子们》（1970年开播）莎拉瑞妮
From One Life to Live, Mary Lauren Bishop. All My Children, Sarah Renee.
《我们的日子》洁西卡艾许丽
And from Days of our Lives, Jessica Ashley.
得奖的是：
And the winner is:
洁西卡艾许丽《我们的日子》
Jessica Ashley from Days of our Lives.
不幸地，洁西卡今晚因故无法出席…
Unfortunately, Jessica couldn't be with us tonight...
我要代表她接受这个奖
...so I'll accept this award on her behalf.
我相信洁西卡…
And I'm sure that Jessica...
会想谢谢我的父母…
...wants to thank my parents...
他们一直都很支持我
...who always believed in me.
她也感谢我的朋友
She'd also like to thank my friends:
钱德，莫妮卡，罗斯，菲比，跟瑞秋…
Chandler, Monica, Ross, Phoebe and Rachel...
她就坐在那边
...who's sitting right there.
我们为什么要急着离开?
Why'd we rush out so fast?
我正好要找卢克和劳拉 在苏珊卢斯的纸巾上签名
I was this close to getting Luke and Laura to sign Susan Lucci's toilet paper.
我们得赶快离开，因为...你看我拿了什么回家!
We had to get out of there because... Look what I won!
我的天啊，你偷走她的奖杯!
Oh, my God. You stole her award!
不…我代表她收下它
No, no, no. I'm accepting it on her behalf.
我想你不知道“代表”是什么意思
I don't think you know what "behalf" means.
我当然知道，它是个动词 意思是“我能分一半”
Sure I do. It's a verb. As in "I be half it"!
-你得把它还回去 -我应该得奖的，我真的好想得奖
- You've got to take this back. - I should've won. I really wanted it.
她根本不在乎才没有出席 它也可以拿来当格莱美
She didn't care enough to come to the thing. It could also be a Grammy.
不，乔伊
No, Joey.
没有人看到我把它拿走 整个桌子上都是奖杯
No one saw me take it. There's a whole table of them.
你想要一个不属于你的奖杯吗?
Do you want an award you didn't win?
不，我想要一个属于我的奖杯 但没有人愿意让我得奖
No, I want an award I did win. But nobody's given me any of those!
如果我把它摆在这里，大家就会看到它…
If I put it up, when people come over, they'll see it...
以为我真的得奖了
...and think I won it.
乔伊，上面写着“最佳女配角奖”
Joey, it says "Best Supporting Actress."
我可以把那个刮掉
I can scratch that right off.
这是不对的，你得把它还回去
This is wrong. You have to take it back.
你不会想这样把奖杯拿回家 你真的有演戏天份
You don't want to win an award this way.You're very talented.
有一天你会真的得奖 那对你来说才有意义
Someday you'll win one of these for real and that one will mean something.
-好吧 -好吗? 谢谢
- Oh, all right. - All right? Thank you.
-我明天就把它还回去 -谢谢
- I'll take it back tomorrow. - Thank you.
如果我不能拥有它，你也不能拥有它!
If I can't have it, you can't have it!
-盖勒教授? -路易斯? 有什么事吗?
- Professor Geller?- Yes, Mr. Lewis? How can I help you?
我知道我的期中考没有考好
I know I didn't do well on my midterms and stuff.
但我希望你能帮我改成绩
But I was hoping you could change my grade.
我为什么要那么做?
And why, exactly, would I do that?
因为我爱上你了
Because I'm in love with you.
什么?
What?
对，我爱上你了
Yeah. I'm all in love with you and stuff.
-你可以帮我改成绩吗? -不行
- So could you change my grade? - No!
为什么? 你帮奈德改成绩
Why not? You changed Ned's grade.
那不一样，因为他真的爱上我了
That's different. Because he was actually in love with me.
不，他才没有! 他只是在耍你
No, he's not! He's totally yanking your chain.
他已经用这一招对付过其他三个教授
He's done this with three other teachers.
-什么? -他有女朋友
- What? - He's got a girlfriend.
我不敢相信有人会为了成绩那么做
I can't believe someone would do that for a grade.
我知道
I know.
那太可怕了
It's awful.
我爱你
I love you.
-好吧 -什么? 是真的
- All right. - What? It's true.
-噢，上帝 -你爱我? 你爱我?
Oh, God... Okay. Oh, you love me? You love me?
好吧．你这么爱我，过来亲我吧
All right, fine. You love me so much, come over here and give me a kiss.
你得了80分! 没有不及格! 有点自尊吧!
You got an 80! You didn't even fail! Have some self-respect!
-你看到钱德了吗? -没有，怎么了？
- Have you seen Chandler? - No, why?
我一直在想我会失去的一切
I keep thinking about all the things I won't have.
我真的吓坏了，我不知道该怎么办
It's freaking me out. I don't know what to do.
别担心
Don't sweat it.
钱德不在，别管那么多规矩，那个男的很帅
Chandler's not around, so get it out of your system. That guy's cute.
别这样，我是认真的
Come on, I'm serious.
-我得跟他谈这件事 -你真的不该那么做
- I've got to talk to him about this. - That's the last thing you want to do.
-为什么? -因为你要嫁给他!
- Why? - Because you're marrying him!
你得帮帮我
You gotta help me out here.
我从来没有订过婚，也没有结过婚
I've never been engaged. I've never really been married.
我只能告诉你我妈跟我说的话
I can only tell you what my mother told me.
当你对一段关系有疑虑害怕或焦虑时…
When you have doubts or fears or anxieties about a relationship...
别跟你的丈夫沟通这些问题
...don't communicate them to your husband.
我不该跟我要共度一生的男人…
I'm not supposed to share my doubts and fears...
分享我的疑虑跟恐惧?
...with the guy I'm spending the rest of my life with?
没错，就是那样
That is correct. Yes.
你应该把那件事埋在心里…
You're supposed to put all that stuff in a little box in your mind...
永远不再提
...and lock it up.
-那是你妈妈告诉你的? -对
- Your mother told you this? - Yes.
那个结了很多次婚 在你十三岁时她就自杀了的女人?
The woman who married a bunch of times and killed herself when you were 13?
我的天啊，你说的对
Oh, my God, you're right.
去告诉钱德，快点，免得太迟了!
Tell Chandler. Hurry, before it's too late!
等一下，这也表示放荡是得不到真爱的吗?
Wait! Does this also mean that putting out doesn't get you love?
-我不信我要跟洁西卡艾许丽碰面! -等一下
- I'm gonna meet Jessica Ashley! - Wait, wait.
瑞秋，拜托你冷静一点，好吗？ 我跟这个女人一起工作
Rach, please be cool, okay? I work with this woman.
好吧，我会很冷静的
Okay, I'm totally cool.
请进
Come in.
-嘿，洁西卡 -嘿，洁西
- Hey, Jessica. - Hey, Jess.
她是我朋友瑞秋
This is my friend Rachel.
-嘿 -好吗?
- Hi. - What's up?
这是你的肥皂奖，我代表你收下了它
Here's your Soapie. I accepted it for you.
我的天啊，我得奖了? 你知道这代表什么意义吗？
Oh, my God. I won? Do you have any idea what this means?
你不把它摆在柜子里吗?
You're not gonna put it on your shelf or anything?
不，我只想把真正的奖杯摆在柜子里，失陪了
No, I try to save that for real awards. Now if you'll excuse me?
-要把它拿回去吗? -那当然
- Take it back? - Absolutely.
对，做的好!
Yeah, you do!
甜心? 我们快结婚了…
Honey? As we get closer to the wedding...
有什么事你想跟我分享吗?
...is there anything you'd like to share?
好吧，我觉得桌上的装饰太大了
Okay. I think the centerpieces are too big.
你错了，桌上的装饰刚刚好
You're wrong. The centerpieces are fine.
-你曾经觉得害怕过吗? -有一点，它们真的很大
- Do you ever get scared at all? - Kind of. They're really big.
你不害怕自己没办法再认识新的人吗?
Doesrt it freak you out that you'll never be with anybody new again?
什么?
What?
我非常爱你
I love you so much.
有时候我会很难过我无法再有那样的感觉
Sometimes it bothers me that I'll never have that feeling.
当你刚订识一个人…
When you first meet someone...
你会觉得新鲜刺激 你知道那种心动的感觉吗
...and it's new and exciting. You know that rush?
不，当我刚认识一个人…
No, when I first meet somebody...
我会觉得慌张，焦虑，满头大汗
...it's mostly panic, anxiety and a great deal of sweating.
好吧，但你是男人
Okay. But you're a guy.
你不害怕你永远不能再跟别人上床吗?
Arert you freaked out that you'll never sleep with anybody else?
不能跟别人上床，不
Sleeping with somebody, no.
我害怕的是焦虑，慌张，跟满头大汗
Anxiety, panic and, I'm afraid, even more sweating.
即使是跟我在一起?
Even with me?
我们刚开始交往的六个月，我严重脱水
I was dangerously dehydrated the first six months of our relationship.
对我来说心动的感觉是我们会共度余生
For me, the rush is knowing that we'll be together the rest of our lives.
-真的吗? -对
- Really? - Well, yeah.
知道你有这些想法 我们又回到了慌张，焦虑跟...
Knowing you're having these thoughts, we're back to panic, anxiety and...
我真的需要喝点运动饮料
...l'll definitely need some kind of sports drink.
过来，你不必担心
Come here. Oh, you don't have to worry.
而且你知道吗? 跟你在一起我一定能遇上新鲜的事
Besides, you know what? I'll have a lot of new things with you.
我们第一次买房子 第一个孩子，第一个孙子
The first time we buy a house. Our first kid. Our first grandkid.
给我水，快点
Water. Water. Water.
摩斯? 我能跟你谈谈吗?
Mr. Morse? Can I speak to you for a moment?
你今天上课的内容很精彩 你剪了头发吗?
That was a great lecture today. Did you get a little haircut?
对，你喜欢吗? 你爱吗?
Yeah, yeah. Do you like it? Do you love it?
我要告诉你我会把你的成绩改回来
I want you to know I'm changing your grade back.
什么? 为什么?
What? Why?
我知道你在搞什么鬼 那是行不通的
I know what you're trying to pull here. It won't work.
我没有搞鬼，听着，我爱你
I'm not trying to pull anything. Look, I love you, dude.
我甚至不想谈这件事 这个小“事”结束了
I'm not even gonna talk about this. This little "thing" is over.
我知道你有女朋友，也知道其他教授的事
I know you have a girlfriend. And I know about the other professors.
你觉得那会让我有什么感觉？ 你利用我!
How do you think that makes me feel? You used me!
你不爱我，你从来都没有爱过我!
You don't love me and you never did!
温斯顿教授，佛迪瑞克森教授
Professor Winston. Professor Frederickson.
我马上来
I'll be right with you.
别让事情变得更糟糕 我会给你“C”，可以走了吗
Don't make this worse and I'll give you a "C." Shall we?
-瑞秋。-我马上来
I'll be out in a second.
这真的是太意外了
"It's just so unexpected!
我得告诉大家 被提名诺贝尔奖…
I'll tell you, it's such an honor to just be nominated...
已经是莫大的光荣
...for a Nobel Prize.
我竟然因为按摩得了诺贝尔奖!
And, you know, to win one for a massage!
特别是我刚拿下东尼奖 （美国百老汇舞台剧界最高荣誉奖）的最佳女演员奖…
Especially just after winning a Tony Award for Best Actress..."
我们订了八点的位置
Our reservations are at 8.
以《我们订了八点的位置》得奖，编剧是尼尔赛门
"...in Reservations at Eight by Neil Simon.
谢谢你，尼尔，谢谢你帮我写台词
Thank you, Neil. Thank you for the words."
快点结束吧，我们要迟到了
Finish this later. We're gonna be late.
请不要奏乐，还有一件事
Please don't play the music. Just one more thing.
“纽约现场直播 欢迎收看《周六夜现场》”（NBC娱乐王牌节目）
"Live from New York, it's Saturday Night!"